Guide to the Leo Lerman papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1923-1995
  - Fitch, Noel Riley, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Fitzgerald, Geraldine, 1976-1987 (Box 6)
  - Fitzgerald, Olda, 1991-1992 (Box 6)
  - Fitzpatrick, Mariana, 1971-1980 (Box 6)
  - Fitzsimmons, Mae, 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Fizdale, Robert and Gold, Arthur, 1954-1984 (Box 6)
  - Fleishman, Joel L., 1972-1983 (Box 6)
  - Fleming, Ann Taylor, 1977-1980 (Box 6)
  - Fleming, Eden and Marston, 1966-1978 (Box 6)
  - Fletcher, Richard, 1957-1961 (Box 6)
  - Flexner, Marion, 1954-1958 (Box 6)
  - Flusser, Richard Stuart, 1957-1964 (Box 6)
  - Fonteyn, Margot, 1949-1976 (Box 6)
  - Forbes, Elizabeth, 1965-1973 (Box 6)
  - Forbes-Robertson, Dinah, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Ford, Betty and Gerald, 1974-1977 (Box 6)
  - Ford, Charles Henri, 1944-1983 (Box 6)
  - Foss, Lukas and Cornelia, 1977-1984 (Box 7)
  - Fosse, Bob (Robert), 1957-1964 (Box 7)
  - Foster, James and Ethelwyne, 1982-1991 (Box 7)
  - Fox, Angela, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Fox, Joe, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Foy Family, 1956-1976 (Box 7)
  - Foy, Faye, 1954-1984 (Box 7)
  - Foy, Gray, 1948-1986, (15 Folders) (Box 7)
  - Foy, Vivian Duncan, 1968-1974 (Box 7)
  - France, Richard, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Franchetti, Christina, 1978-1984 (Box 7)
  - Francine, Anne, 1963-1989 (Box 7)
  - Francis, Muriel, 1950-1966 (Box 7)
  - Frankenberg, Lloyd, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1966-1993 (Box 7)
  - Frankfurt, Suzie, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - Fraser, Kennedy, 1989-1992 (Box 7)
  - Fratti, Mario and Laura, 1964-1984 (Box 7)
  - Fratti, Valentina, 1964-1987 (Box 7)
  - Freedley, George, 1953-1962 (Box 7)
  - Fremantle, Anne, 1948-1974 (Box 7)
  - French, Herbert, 1936-1983 (Box 7)
  - Freund, Gisele, undated (Box 7)
  - Friedman-Kien, Alvin, 1971-1976 (Box 7)
  - Frost, Eunice, 1958-1959 (Box 7)
  - Fuchs, Anne Sutherland, 1988-1993 (Box 7)
  - Ga-Go, 1955-1994, (3 Folders) (Box 7)
  - Gr-Gy,1948-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 8)
  - Gaba, Lester, 1933-1987 (Box 8)
  - Galassi, Jonathan, 1982-1990 (Box 8)
  - Gandee, Charles, 1989-1994 (Box 8)
  - Ganz, Julian and Jo Ann, 1981-1993 (Box 8)
  - Garfinkel, Jane, 1972-1976 (Box 8)
  - Gaspinetti, Luigi, 1971-1973 (Box 8)
  - Gasser, Manüel, 1971-1974 (Box 8)
  - Gaussen, Sibylle, 1977-1983 (Box 8)
  - Gavin, James, 1987-1991 (Box 8)
  - Gay, Peter, 1982-1984 (Box 8)
  - Gaynes, George and McLerie, Allyn Ann, 1956-1992 (Box 8)
  - Germond, Arthur, 1970-1973 (Box 8)
  - Gersh, Gloria, 1977-1980 (Box 8)
  - Gendel, Milton and Evelyn, 1944-1982 (Box 8)
  - Gerson, Joan Nathan, 1985-1990 (see also: Joan Nathan file) (Box 8)
  - Gielgud, John, 1959-1994 (Box 8)
  - Gill, Brendan, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Gill, Jill, 1965-1978 (Box 8)
  - Gilliatt, Penelope, 1965-1984 (Box 8)
  - Gilman, Howard, 1970-1994 (Box 8)
  - Gish, Lillian, 1960-1994 (Box 8)
  - Glasberg, Rita, 1931-1984 (Box 8)
  - Glenville, Peter, 1957-1967 (Box 8)
  - Gochman, Alice, 1988-1991 (Box 8)
  - Goldberger, Paul, 1989-1993 (Box 8)
  - Golde, Morris, 1959-1982 (Box 8)
  - Goldman, Milton, 1960-1985 (Box 8)
  - Goldwasser Family, 1927-1990 (Box 8)
  - Goldwasser, David and Ida, 1933-1983 (Box 8)
  - Goldwasser, Irving and Minnie, 1926-1977 (Box 8)
  - Goldswasser, Larry, 1936 (Box 8)
  - Goldswasser, Lew, 1945-1981 (Box 8)
  - Goldswasser, Martin and Electa, 1925-1994 (Box 8)
  - Goldswasser, Pat, 1968-1972 (Box 8)
  - Goldwasser, Norma and Rosalie, 1925-1980 (Box 8)
  - Gomez, Edward, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Gordon, Ruth, 1949-1979 (Box 8)
  - Goth, Trudy, 1950-1952 (Box 8)
  - Gottlieb, Morton, 1959-1980 (Box 8)
  - Gottlieb, Robert, 1985-1992 (Box 8)
  - Gould, Diana, 1958-1967 (Box 8)
  - Gourlay, Gilda, 1984-1985 (Box 8)
  - Goyen, William, 1949-1957 (Box 8)
  - Graffman, Gary and Naomi, 1971-1987 (Box 8)
  - Graham, Dora, 1950-1957 (Box 8)
  - Grant, Cary, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Graver, Melanie and Ben, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Gray, Cleve, 1959-1990 (Box 8)
  - Gray, Francine, 1956-1990 (Box 8)
  - Green, Adolph, 1967-1991 (Box 8)
  - Green, Constance (Connie) Morrow, 1961-1970 (Box 8)
  - Green, Sam, 1968-1985 (Box 8)
  - Greene, Alison, 1968-1978 (Box 8)
  - Greene, Bert, 1963-1975 (Box 8)
  - Greene, Stephen, 1944-1975 (Box 8)
  - Gregory, Andre and Chiquita, 1973-1989 (Box 9)
  - Gregory, Jamee, 1972-1975 (Box 9)
  - Gregory, Lydia and George, 1971-1981 (Box 9)
  - Grey, Joel, 1967-1987 (Box 9)
  - Grimes, Tammy, 1964-1985 (Box 9)
  - Gronowicz, Antoni, 1973-1978 (Box 9)
  - Gross, Amy, 1964-1992 (Box 9)
  - Gross, John, 1983-1987 (Box 9)
  - Grossinger, Florence, 1957-1976 (Box 9)
  - Guimares, Dona, 1968-1991 (Box 9)
  - Gunther, Jane and John, 1931-1963 (Box 9)
  - Ha, 1939-1994, (4 Folders) (Box 9)
  - Hadfield, John, 1962-1965 (Box 9)
  - Hagan, Uta, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Hahn, Hannelore, 1958-1994 (Box 9)
  - Haines, Howard, 1970-1983 (Box 9)
  - Haines, Iris, 1951-1992 (Box 9)
  - Halbmeier, Eddie, Margaret, and Susan, 1931-1991 (Box 9)
  - Halbmeier, Eugenia, 1946-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 9)
  - Hambleton, T. Edward, 1957-1976 (Box 9)
  - Hamilton, Jamie, 1955-1965 (Box 9)
  - Handman, Wynn, 1972-1993 (Box 9)
  - Hanff, Helene, 1972-1985 (Box 9)
  - Hanley, Ed, 1937-1950 (Box 9)
  - Hanna, Brian, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - Harari, Denyse, 1946-1990 (Box 9)
  - Hardwick, Elizabeth, 1977-1989 (Box 9)
  - Harlech, Pamela, 1953-1993 (Box 9)
  - Harman, Eve, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Harnick, Sheldon, 1964-1994 (Box 9)
  - Harrington, Curtis, 1985-1991 (Box 9)
  - Harris, Julie, 1951-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 9)
  - Harris, Rosemary1958-1973 (Box 9)
  - Harris, Warren, 1972-1981 (Box 9)
  - Hart, Moss, 1960-1961 (Box 10)
  - Hatfield, Hurd, 1970-1995 (Box 10)
  - Havoc, June, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
  - Haydn, Hiram, 1949-1959 (Box 10)
  - Hayes, Helen, 1972-1980 (Box 10)
  - Hayward, Brooke, 1976-1984 (Box 10)
  - Hazard, Eloise, 1942-1947 (Box 10)
  - Heal, Edith, 1950-1987 (Box 10)
  - Hecht, Anthony, 1981-1991 (Box 10)
  - Hecht, Helen, 1981-1983 (Box 10)
  - Heilpern, John, 1965-1992 (Box 10)
  - Heller, Red, 1949-1952 (Box 10)
  - Hellman, Lillian, 1959-1970 (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Andrea, 1982-1986 (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Mary, 1970-1992 (Box 10)
  - Henning, Margaret Evelyn, 1930-1953 (Box 10)
  - Henry, Mary Roblee, 1983-1989 (Box 10)
  - Herman, Jerry, 1978-1987 (Box 10)
  - Hepburn, Katharine, 1984-1990 (Box 10)
  - Herlie, Eileen, 1953-1974 (Box 10)
  - Herlihy, James Leo, 1965-1969 (Box 10)
  - Herz, Shirley, 1994 (Box 10)
  - Hirschfeld, Al and Dolly Haas, 1931-1985 (Box 10)
  - Hirst, Edna, 1971-1984 (Box 10)
  - Hobson, Jade, 1976-1988 (Box 10)
  - Hochman, Sandra, 1965-1988 (Box 10)
  - Hockney, David, 1988-1990 (Box 10)
  - Hodge, Patricia, 1983-1992 (Box 10)
  - Hogan, Mimi, 1960-1965 (Box 10)
  - Hogg, Min, 1988-1992 (Box 10)
  - Hogrefe, Jeffrey, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Holbrooke, Blythe, 1981-1983 (Box 10)
  - Holland, David, 1984-1997 (Box 10)
  - Hollander, John 1975-1984 (Box 10)
  - Holm, Celeste, 1963-1992 (Box 10)
  - Holm, Hanya, 1955-1958 (Box 10)
  - Holmquist, Bounce, 1939-1956 (Box 10)
  - Holmquist, Karline, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Hope, Vida, 1956-19591972-1992 (Box 10)
  - Horowitz, Vladimir and Wanda Toscanini, 1974-1988 (Box 10)
  - Horst, Horst B.1972-1991 (Box 10)
  - Hoskwith, Arnold, 1972-1983 (Box 10)
  - Houghton, Jerry, 1948-1975 (Box 10)
  - Houghton, Morris, 1955-1960 (Box 10)
  - Hovis, Gene, 1978-1987 (Box 10)
  - Houseman, John and Joan, 1958-1990 (Box 10)
  - Howard, Jean, 1983-1990 (Box 10)
  - Howard, Peter, 1977-1992 (Box 10)
  - Howe, Helen, 1954-1973 (Box 10)
  - Howe, Molly, 1956-1967 (Box 10)
  - Hubert, Lenny and Karen Allison, 1982-1994 (Box 10)
  - Hucliez, Marielle, 1981-1992 (Box 10)
  - Huffington, Arianna Stassinopoulos, 1981-1986 (Box 10)
  - Hughes, Maebelle, 1957-1984 (Box 10)
  - Hunter, Nancy, 1954-1960 (Box 10)
  - Hunter, Richard, undated, 1940s-1990s, (15 Folders) (Box 26)
  - Hunter, Sylvia, 1950-1980 (Box 10)
  - Hurok, Sol, 191957-1972 (Box 10)
  - Hurst, Fannie, 1959-1961 (Box 10)
  - Hutton, Lauren, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1970-1987 (Box 10)
  - Hyams, Barry, 1950-1963 (Box 10)
  - I, 1933-1992 (Box 10)
  - Imbs, Braving, 1943- (Box 10)
  - Imbs, Valeska, 1944-1949 (Box 10)
  - Ingalsbee, Winifred, 1934-1951 (Box 10)
  - Inge, William, 1949-1964 (Box 10)
  - Irons, Jeremy, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Irving, Robert, 1958-1958 (Box 10)
  - J, 1946-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 11)
  - Jablons, Beverly, 1977-1983 (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Robert, 1976-1978 (Box 11)
  - Jacobs, Neil, 1992-1994 (Box 11)
  - Jagendorf, Moritz, 1951-1954 (Box 11)
  - Jamail, Stephen, 1980-1984 (Box 11)
  - James, Charles, 1952-1966 (Box 11)
  - James, Edward, 1951 (Box 11)
  - Janeway, Carol, 1943-1945 (Box 11)
  - Janis, Sidney, 1944-1984 (Box 11)
  - Janklow, Morton, 1980-1988 (Box 11)
  - Jenks, Sally Porter, 1951-1962 (Box 11)
  - Jensky, Toby, 1968-1982 (Box 11)
  - Joel, Lydia, 1958-1992 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Buffie, 1946-1984 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Katharine, 1987-1990 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Philip, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Ray, 1955-1983 (Box 11)
  - Jones, Judith, 1984-1992 (Box 11)
  - Jong, Erica, 1976-1984 (Box 11)
  - Joseph, Robert, L., 1956-1962 (Box 11)
  - Julien, Jay, 1952-1975 (Box 11)
  - K, 1930-1994, (2 Folders) (Box 11)
  - Kafka, Barbara Poses1960-1992 (Box 11)
  - Kalstone, David, 1978-1983 (Box 11)
  - Kaminsky, Howard, 1984-1994 (Box 11)
  - Kander, John, 1968-1991 (Box 11)
  - Kanin, Garson, 1960-1989 (Box 11)
  - Kapp, Walter, 1933-1943 (Box 11)
  - Karmason, Marilyn G., 1985-1992 (Box 11)
  - Karroll, Lillie, 1974-1977 (Box 11)
  - Kasper, Herbert, 1969-1985 (Box 11)
  - Kaufman, Robert, 1987-1992 (Box 11)
  - Kay, Beatrice, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Danny and Sylvia Fine, 1963-1986 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Dena, 1970-1983 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Joel, 1971-1990 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Nora, 1950-1984 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Ellen, 1978-1989 (Box 11)
  - Kaye, Sidney, 1958-1960 (Box 11)
  - Kazin, Pearl, 1947-1952 (Box 11)
  - Keene, Frances, 1951-1982 (Box 11)
  - Keller, Dominick, 1977-1983 (Box 11)
  - Kelly, Lawrence (Larry), 1956-1972 (Box 11)
  - Kent, Princess Michael of, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Kepler, Doris and Leo, 1960-1965 (Box 11)
  - Kiesler, Steffi and Frederick, 1943-1955 (Box 11)
  - Kinross, Patrick, 1964-1988 (Box 11)
  - Kinsey, John, 1972-1978 (Box 11)
  - Kinsler, Richard, 1987-1992 (Box 11)
  - Kirschbaum, Emilie, 1951-1964 (Box 11)
  - Kirschbaum, Louise, 1951-1965 (Box 11)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1952-1984 (Box 11)
  - Kiser, Elizabeth Otis, 1952-1973 (Box 11)
  - Kiss, Esther Pallas, 1942-1969 (Box 11)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1976-1982 (Box 11)
  - Klein, Elaine, 1975-1983 (Box 11)
  - Klein, Sylvia, 1926-1936 (Box 11)
  - Kline, Kevin, 1982-1986 (Box 11)
  - Klotz, Florence, 1982-1987 (Box 11)
  - Koch, John and Dora, 1958-1978 (Box 11)
  - Koch, Stephen, 1983-1988 (Box 11)
  - Kochnitzky, Leon, 1947-1983 (Box 11)
  - Koda, Harold, 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Kollsman, Luli von Honberg (Luli Deste), 1946-1949 (Box 11)
  - Korda, Michael, 1966-1984 (Box 11)
  - Kornfled, Albert, 1948-1949 (Box 11)
  - Kosner, Edward, 1983-1993 (Box 11)
  - Kraft, Gilman, 1965-1992 (Box 11)
  - Krantz, Judith, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Krawitz, Herman, 1960-1967 (Box 11)
  - Kreisberg, Luisa, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Kronburg, Sasha, 1940 (Box 11)
  - Kronenberger, Louis and Emmy, 1952-1969 (Box 11)
  - Kummer, Corby, 1982-1985 (Box 11)
  - Kushner, Tony, 1993 (Box 11)
  - L, 1945-1993 (Box 12)
  - Labro, Françoise, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
  - Lahr, John, 1976-1994 (Box 12)
  - Laing, Hugh, 1952-1983 (Box 12)
  - Lamb, Patricia, 1957-1988 (Box 12)
  - Lambert, Evelyn and Joseph, 1971-1992 (Box 12)
  - Lamkin, Speed, 1930-1951 (Box 12)
  - Landers, Ann, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Landesman, Knight and Carol, 1975-1994 (Box 12)
  - Landesman, Paula, 1972-1986 (Box 12)
  - Landesman, Rocco, 1983-1992 (Box 12)
  - Landshoff, Hermann, 1949-1952 (Box 12)
  - Landshoff, Ursula, 1949-1960 (Box 12)
  - Landshoff, Werner, 1957-1966 (Box 12)
  - Lane, Allen, 1952-1965 (Box 12)
  - Lane, Joe, 1976-1981 (Box 12)
  - Lang, George, 1979-1990 (Box 12)
  - Lang, Robert, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Langner, Lawrence, 1958-1959 (Box 12)
  - Langton, Basil, 1984-1988 (Box 12)
  - Lansbury, Angela, 1977-1983 (Box 12)
  - Lanux, Eyre de, 1951-1952 (Box 12)
  - Lantz, Robert, 1972-1988 (Box 12)
  - Lapham, Robert, 1979-1991 (Box 12)
  - Lapine, James, 1987-1994 (Box 12)
  - Larkin, Robert, 1977-1983 (Box 12)
  - Larson, Jack, 1973-1978 (Box 12)
  - Lassalle, Nancy, 1949-1984 (Box 12)
  - Latham, John, 1977-1983 (Box 12)
  - Latouche, John, 1941-1949 (Box 12)
  - Latour, Martine, 1966-1986 (Box 12)
  - Lauder, Estee, 1978-1990 (Box 12)
  - Lauder, Leonard and Evelyn, 1983-1990 (Box 12)
  - Laughlin, Clarence John, 1949 (Box 12)
  - Laughlin, James, 1949-1993 (Box 12)
  - Laurence, Paula, 1950-1985, (3 Folders) (Box 12)
  - Laurents, Arthur, 1951-1991 (Box 12)
  - Lauritzen, Peter, 1973-1992 (Box 12)
  - Lauritzen, Rose, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Lawford, Nicholas, 1969-1984 (Box 12)
  - Lax, Robert (Box 12)
  - Lay, Virginia, 1986-1993 (Box 12)
  - Lear, Evelyn and Thomas Stewart, 1970-1982 (Box 12)
  - LeBell, June, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
  - Le Bourhis, Katell, 1984-1989 (Box 12)
  - Lebowitz, Fran, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Lecesne, James, 1990-1994 (Box 13)
  - Lee, Richard, 1983-1993 (Box 13)
  - Lehmann, John, 1949-1974 (Box 13)
  - Lehmann, Robert, 1974-1991 (Box 13)
  - Leigh, Dorian, 1948-1992 (Box 13)
  - Leigh, Julian, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Leigh, Vivian, 1963 (Box 13)
  - Leighton, Margaret, 1956-1967 (Box 13)
  - Lenya, Lotte, 1959-1976 (Box 13)
  - Leopold, Helen, 1954-1958 (Box 13)
  - Lerman, Ellen, 1962-1980 (Box 13)
  - Lerman, Ida, 1927-1978, (4 Folders) (Box 13)
  - Lerman, Ida-- cards to Ida Lerman from others (Box 13)
  - Lerman, Leo-- to family, 1929-1978 (Box 13)
  - Lerman, Leo-- to Richard Hunter, undated and 1941-1988 (Box 27-28)
  - Lerman Family, 1935-1992 (Box 13)
  - Lerner, Alan Jay, 1960-1973 (Box 13)
  - Lerner, Max, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
  - LeRoy, Warner, 1976-1987 (Box 13)
  - Lescher, Robert, 1957-1991 (Box 13)
  - Leser, Bernard, 1978-1994 (Box 13)
  - Levine, Phyllis Lee, 1934-1983 (Box 13)
  - Levine, Rhoda, 1959-1971 (Box 13)
  - Levy, Martin David, 1963-1964 (Box 13)
  - Levy, Paul, 1992-1994 (Box 13)
  - Lewis, Robert, 1957-1983 (Box 13)
  - Liagre, Alfred de. 1963-1977 (Box 13)
  - Liberman, Alexander, 1962-1992 (Box 13)
  - Libin, Paul, 1975-1992 (Box 13)
  - Lieberson, Brigitta and Goddard, 1951-1987 (Box 13)
  - Lieberson, Jonathan, 1979-1984 (Box 13)
  - Lindamood, Peter, 1950-1967 (Box 13)
  - Lindfors, Viveca, 1973-1977 (Box 13)
  - Lindley, Hilda, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Linscott, Robert, 1950-1958 (Box 13)
  - Lippe, Ashwan and Simone, 1958-1969 (Box 13)
  - Lippman, Allen I., 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Lipton, James, 1950-1992 (Box 13)
  - List, Sissy, 1989-1992 (Box 13)
  - Locke, Edith Raymond, 1961-1991 (Box 14)
  - Logan, Joshua and Nedda Harrigan, 1969-1989 (Box 14)
  - London, George, 1957-972 (Box 14)
  - Long, William Ivey, 1992 (Box 14)
  - Loon, Gerard Willem van, 1952-1970 (Box 14)
  - Loos, Anita, 1954-1989 (Box 14)
  - Loos, Mary, 1937-1992 (Box 14)
  - Losch, Tilly, 1957-1963 (Box 14)
  - Loud, Ruth McAneny, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Loudon, Dorothy, 1980-1986 (Box 14)
  - Loverd, William, 1977-1992 (Box 14)
  - Lowe, Charles, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Lucarda, Marjorie, 1984-1990 (Box 14)
  - Lupone, Patti, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Lundholm, Roy, 1945-1955 (Box 14)
  - Lust, Herbert and Barbara, 1955-1962 (Box 14)
  - Lyndon, Andrew, 1947-1977 (Box 14)
  - Lynes, Russell, 1949-1955 (Box 14)
  - Lyon, Anne, 1980-1989 (Box 14)
  - Lyons, Jeffrey, Judy and Benjamin, 1979-1984 (Box 14)
  - Lyons, Leonard and Sylvia, 1961-1988 (Box 14)
  - M, 1943-1994, (8 Folders) (Box 14)
  - Mackintosh, Robert, 1987-1989 (Box 14)
  - Maclean, Katherine, 1966-1991 (Box 14)
  - MacRae, Joyce, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - MacSweeney, Eve, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Madden, Kathy, 1976-1994 (Box 14)
  - Magriel, Paul, 1972-1989 (Box 14)
  - Mailer, Norman, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Mander, Lady Rosalie, 1969-1972 (Box 14)
  - Manning, High, 1959-1992 (Box 14)
  - Maremont, Eileen Adler, 1964-1989 (Box 15)
  - Margittai, Tom, 1980-1992 (Box 15)
  - Marlowe, Sylvia, 1951-1979 (Box 15)
  - Martin, Judith, 1982-1984 (Box 15)
  - Martin, Mary, 1977-1985 (Box 15)
  - Martin, Steve, 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - Mason, Felicity, 1976-1984 (Box 15)
  - Mason, Francis, 1964-1983 (Box 15)
  - Mason, James, 1944-1954 (Box 15)
  - Matthau, Walter and Carol, 1988-1992 (Box 15)
  - Max, Peter, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Maxwell, Jerrie, 1931-1974, (2 Folders) (Box 15)
  - Maxwell, William, 1961-1994 (Box 15)
  - McCallum, June, 1974-1991 (Box 15)
  - McCann, Elizabeth, 1975-984 (Box 15)
  - McCann, Mary Ellen, 1991-1994 (Box 15)
  - McCourt, James, 1970-1984 (Box 15)
  - McCowan, Alice, 1975-1991 (Box 15)
  - McCullough, Jeanne, 1980-1983 (Box 15)
  - McDonald, Donald, 1988-1992 (Box 15)
  - McDowall, Roddy, 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - McElroy, David, 1957-1962 (Box 15)
  - McElwaine, Sandra, 1972-1992 (Box 15)
  - McFadden, Frances, 1948-1983 (Box 15)
  - McFadden, Mary, 1978-1993 (Box 15)
  - McGuire, Michael, 1976 (Box 15)
  - McHarg, Yvonne, 1945-1949 (Box 15)
  - McKay, Alice, 1953-1968 (Box 15)
  - McKay, Scott, 1957-1963 (Box 15)
  - McKean, Thomas, 1986-1992 (Box 15)
  - McKechnie, Donna, 1987-1994 (Box 15)
  - McKendry, Maxine de la Falaise, 1972 (Box 15)
  - McKenna, Siobhan, 1957-1959 (Box 15)
  - McLaughlin-Gill, Frances, 1969-1986 (Box 15)
  - McNally, Terrence, 1991-1993 (Box 15)
  - McPhee, Colin, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Marcus, Stanley, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Marion, John, 1987-1994 (Box 15)
  - Markova, Alicia, 1960-1973 (Box 15)
  - Marton, Elisabeth, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Medwick, Cathleen, 1977-1992 (Box 15)
  - Metha, Sonny, 1991-1992 (Box 15)
  - Meier, Richard and Kate, 1974-1993 (Box 15)
  - Mekas, Jonas, 1984-1988 (Box 15)
  - Meltzer, Rosemary Kent, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Mellen, Polly and Henry, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Mello, Dawn, 1982-1986 (Box 15)
  - Menen, Aubrey, 1981-1984 (Box 15)
  - Mennin, Peter and Georgeanne, 1972-1989 (Box 15)
  - Menotti, Gian-Carlo, 1952-1964 (Box 15)
  - Merchant, Ismael, Ivory, and James, 1963-1993 (Box 15)
  - Merkin, Daphne, 1983-1985 (Box 15)
  - Messinesi, Despina, 1972-1988 (Box 15)
  - Michaels, Duane, 1964-1968 (Box 15)
  - Michaels, Audrey, 1952-1985 (Box 15)
  - Michener, Charles, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Beatrix, 1973-1993 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Charles, H., 1983-1985 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Henry, 1943-1963 (Box 15)
  - Miller, John, 1968-1987 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Mary Britton (Isabel Bolton), 1947-1952 (Box 15)
  - Miller, Pat, 1984-1990 (Box 15)
  - Miner, Jan, 1976-1988 (Box 15)
  - Minnelli, Liza, 1965 (Box 15)
  - Mirabella, Grace, 1975-1992 (Box 15)
  - Mitchell, Ruth, 1973-1990 (Box 15)
  - Moffo, Anna, 1963-1983 (Box 15)
  - Mondale, Walter and Joan, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Montant, Jane, 1985-1993 (Box 15)
  - Moore, Honor, 1980-1991 (Box 15)
  - Moore, Jacqui, 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Moore, Marianne, 1952-1958 (Box 15)
  - Moore, Tom and Nonnie, 1970-1992 (Box 15)
  - Moriarty, Michael, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
  - Morris, Edita and Ira, 1947-1952 (Box 15)
  - Morris, Jan, 1977-1989 (Box 16)
  - Morris, Sylvia Jukes, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Mortin, Phyllis and Digby, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Mosell, Fritz, Roder, and Hellmut, 1945-1956 (Box 16)
  - Moss, Howard, 1976-1986 (Box 16)
  - Moss, Stanley, 1942-1953 (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Michael Tyson, 1981-1986 (Box 16)
  - Myerson, Bess, 1973-1983 (Box 16)
  - N, 1939-1992 (Box 16)
  - Nabokov, Nicolas and Dominique, 1969-1988 (Box 16)
  - Nathan, Fred, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Nathan, Joan (see also: Joan Nathan Gerson file), 1984-1993 (Box 16)
  - Neal, Barbara, 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Indiana, 1987-1991 (Box 16)
  - Nemy, Enid, 1983-1988 (Box 16)
  - Nesbitt, Cathleen, 1950-1975 (Box 16)
  - Neway, Patricia, 1953-1964 (Box 16)
  - Newhouse, Jonathan and Pamela, 1968-1991 (Box 16)
  - Newhouse, Donald and Susan, 1968-1993 (Box 16)
  - Newhouse, Sam and Mitzi, 1952-1982 (Box 16)
  - Newhouse, S.I. Jr. and Victoria, 1977-1994 (Box 16)
  - Newhouse, Steve, 1991-1993 (Box 16)
  - Newman, Annalee, 1970-1993 (Box 16)
  - Newman, Bruce, 1989-1992 (Box 16)
  - Newman, Phyllis (Mrs. Adolph Green), 1976-1986 (Box 16)
  - Nguyen, The-Te, 1994-1995 (Box 16)
  - Nicholls, Judy, 1965 (Box 16)
  - Nin, Anaïs, 1943-1972 (Box 16)
  - Nixon, James, 1952-1969 (Box 16)
  - Northrop, Peggy, 1991-1994 (Box 16)
  - Nonkin, Lesley Jane, 1991-1992 (Box 16)
  - Norman, Dorothy, 1949-1992 (Box 16)
  - Norwich, William, 1983-1992 (Box 16)
  - Nossiter, Cal and Paul, 1957-1958 (Box 16)
  - Novak, Barbara, 1987-1992 (Box 16)
  - Novogrod, Nancy, 1988-1992 (Box 16)
  - O, 1943-1993 (Box 16)
  - Obolensky, Ivan, 1951-1958 (Box 16)
  - O'Connor, Patrick, 1987-1988 (Box 16)
  - O'Donnell, George Marion, 1959 (Box 16)
  - O'Higgins, Patrick, 1948-1973 (Box 16)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline, 1983-1994 (Box 16)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline, 1983-1994 (Box 102)
    (copies of correspondence with Kamande Gatura)
  - O'Neal, Cynthia, 1971-1979 (Box 16)
  - Osato, Sono, 1958-1981 (Box 16)
  - Osborne, Hubert, 1936-1944 (Box 16)
  - O'Shea, John M., 1984 (Box 16)
  - Osman, Scott Matthew, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Ostrander, Sheila, 1958-1968 (Box 16)
  - Ostrow, Stuart, 1963-1978 (Box 16)
  - O'Sullivan, Sonya, 1977-1983 (Box 16)
  - O'Toole, Patricia, 1982-1992 (Box 16)
  - Owens, Patricia and Peter, 1990-1993 (Box 16)
  - Owens, Robert, 1958-1965 (Box 16)
  - Oz, Frank, 1978 (Box 16)
  - P, 1945-1994 (Box 17)
  - Packer, Bill, 1983-1991 (Box 17)
  - Page, Ruth, 1954-1958 (Box 17)
  - Paige, Marvin, 1983-1987 (Box 17)
  - Pakula, Alan J. and Hannah, 1958-1992 (Box 17)
  - Palffy, Eleanor, 1949-1950 (Box 17)
  - Pallavicini, Frederico, 1962-1986 (Box 17)
  - Pandit, Rita, 1949 (Box 17)
  - Papp, Joseph, 1965-1991 (Box 17)
  - Parke, Alfred, 1972-1978 (Box 17)
  - Parker, David Shannon, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Parker, Mary, 1952-1971 (Box 17)
  - Parefsky, Benjamin, 1987-1993 (Box 17)
  - Parsons, Betty, 1972-1980 (Box 17)
  - Passante, Nico, 1981-1991 (Box 17)
  - Pate, Edward, 1983-1992 (Box 17)
  - Patent, Caroline Thomas, 1971-1973 (Box 17)
  - Patton, Mary, 1953-1976 (Box 17)
  - Peabody, Elizabeth, 1981-1985 (Box 17)
  - Peale, Norman Vincent, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Peck, Bernice, 1958-1990 (Box 17)
  - Pelle, Marie-Paule, 1973-1990 (Box 17)
  - Pellegrini, Edward, 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Penn, Irving, 1972-1994 (Box 17)
  - Penney, Alexandria, 1989-1994 (Box 17)
  - Peppiatt, Michael, 1985-1994 (Box 17)
  - Perlin, Bernard, 1948-1952 (Box 17)
  - Perper, Kathleen and Leo, 1949-1957 (Box 17)
  - Perry, Frank and Eleanor, 1951-1982 (Box 17)
  - Pesch, Leo, 1985-1994 (Box 17)
  - Peters, Bernadette, 1989-1991 (Box 17)
  - Phillips, John, 1974-1984 (Box 17)
  - Picasso, Paloma, 1979-1993 (Box 17)
  - Pierce, Phoebe, 1948-1950 (Box 17)
  - Platt-Lynnes, George, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Pleasant, Richard, 1948-1954 (Box 17)
  - Pollen, Peregrine, 1961-1978 (Box 17)
  - Pollock, Helen Channing, 1951 (Box 17)
  - Poniatowski, Jean, 1984-1994 (Box 17)
  - Pons, Beatrice, 1950-1985 (Box 17)
  - Pool, Mary Jane, 1983-1992 (Box 17)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1950-1974 (Box 17)
  - Porter, Sheila, 1972-1984 (Box 17)
  - Power, David, 1971-1989 (Box 17)
  - Price, Leontyne, 1964-1977 (Box 17)
  - Price, Robert G., undated (Box 17)
  - Prince, Harold, 1959-1994 (Box 17)
  - Pringle, Aileen, 1952-1980 (Box 17)
  - Pritchett, Dorothy and Victor, 1980-1992 (Box 17)
  - Prokosch, Frederick, 1952-1983 (Box 17)
  - Protas, Ron, 1973-1994 (Box 17)
  - Purdy, James, 1957-1963 (Box 17)
  - Q, 1978-1991 (Box 17)
  - R, 1934-1994, (3 Folders) (Box 18)
  - Rabb, Ellis, 1963-1969 (Box 18)
  - Radkai, Karen, 1978-1985 (Box 18)
  - Radziwill, Lee, 1984-1989 (Box 18)
  - Rainer, Luise, 1945-1991 (Box 18)
  - Rasponi, Conte Lanfranco, 1952-1986 (Box 18)
  - Rathbone, Basil, 1959-1961 (Box 18)